[
    {
      "id": 0,
      "question": "What jersey number Lebron have?",
      "answer": "23",
      "false_answer": "6;24;8",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "What's Lebron's Nickname?",
      "answer": "The King",
      "false_answer": "The Queen;The Qing;Black Mamba",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Who's AD?",
      "answer": "Anthony Davis",
      "false_answer": "Active Directory;Andre Drummond;Andrew Davis",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which is Kobe Bryant's one of favorite movies?",
      "answer": "Whiplash",
      "false_answer": "Lord of the Rings;Ali;Anaconda",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What's the name of Trevor Ariza's child?",
      "answer": "Tajh Ariza",
      "false_answer": "Maj Ariza;Shia Ariza;John Ariza",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What date did Alex Caruso sign with Oklahoma City Thunder?",
      "answer": "9/23/2016",
      "false_answer": "8/16/2015;11/13/2016;1/13/2017",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Why did Alex Caruso shave his head (Hint: Awareness)?",
      "answer": "Donation for testicular cancer research",
      "false_answer": "Donation to his former school; Donation to Church for Tax Deductible;Donation for Democratic Party",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which Player was the most google searched on 3/16/2022?",
      "answer": "Lebron James",
      "false_answer": "Alex Caruso; Russell Westbrook; Magic Johnson",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Who is Kobe's eldest child?",
      "answer": "Natalia Bryant",
      "false_answer": "Gianna Bryant; Capri Bryant;Diamante Bryant",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What date did D'Angelo betray Nick Young?",
      "answer": "3/30/2016",
      "false_answer": "1/2/2016;3/12/2016;12/27/2015",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Who is the last Caucatation Lakers player to make into All-Star Game who's not Pau Gasol? ",
      "answer": "Gail Goodrich",
      "false_answer": "Jerry West; Rudy LaRusso; Gail Goodrich",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Which Player was not voted into 1963 All-Star game?",
      "answer": "Dick GarMaker",
      "false_answer": "Elgin Baylor;Rudy LaRusso;Jerry West",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "How many jerseys did Lakers retire as of 3/19/2022?",
      "answer": "11",
      "false_answer": "7;14;16",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Was Game 6 against Sacramento Kings during 2002 Playoffs rigged?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "false_answer": "No;No;No",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "What was the offensive rating of 2002-03 Lakers team during regular season?",
      "answer": "107.2",
      "false_answer": "108.5;100.4;103;5",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Who is better basketball player?",
      "answer": "Russell Westbrook",
      "false_answer": "Kobe Bryant when he was 2 years old;Kobe Bryant when he was 8 years old; Kobe Bryant when he's literally sleeping",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "What's longest losing streak by Lakers?",
      "answer": "10",
      "false_answer": "6;8;12",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "Who was Kobe Bryant traded for after he was drafted by Charlotte Hornets?",
      "answer": "Vlade Divac",
      "false_answer": "Cash Consideration and 1st Round Pick;Dave Cowns and 2nd Round Pick;1st Round and 2nd Round pick",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "How many techcnial fouls does Shaquille O'Neal have as a player?",
      "answer": "150",
      "false_answer": "88;125;168",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "How much did Kobe Bryant improve on his 3-Points shooting after he cut his afro?",
      "answer": "13%",
      "false_answer": "4%;8%;11%",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "What team was Lakers playing against when Dwight Howard and Steve Nash argue with each other during the game?",
      "answer": "Miami Heat",
      "false_answer": "Cleveland Cavaliers;Houston Rockets;Portland Blazers",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "Who works as a Executive Security Agent for Lakers (As of Sep 2021)?",
      "answer": "Mike Gavaldon III",
      "false_answer": "Frank Thompson;Roland Dore;Andrew Brook",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "Which is correct one for Lakers' official purple color (in Hex)?",
      "answer": "#552583",
      "false_answer": "#3c1a5d;#622b99;#8846cb",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "How many scores did Kobe make on June 9, 2000 against Pacers on NBA Finals?",
      "answer": "2",
      "false_answer": "24;33;51",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Which NBA Finals did Lakers loss to Boston Celtics?",
      "answer": "2010",
      "false_answer": "2011;2013;2009",
      "img": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "When was Jeremy Lin traded to Lakers from Houston Rockets?",
      "answer": "7/13/2014",
      "false_answer": "7/11/2014;7/12/2014;7/14/2014",
      "img": ""
    }
]